Guide to the Bella Abzug papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Subject Files
  - Subseries V.54: Women
    - Abortion: (Box 600)
      - Legislation, 94th Congress; States (Box 605)
      - Military (Box 605)
      - Organizations:
        - General (Box 605)
        - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 605)
        - National Abortion Rights Action League (Box 605)
        - Women's National Abortion Action Coalition (Box 605)
      - Reports--Medical and Statistical; Position Papers (Box 606)
      - Printed (1, 2) (Box 606)
      - Printed (3, 4) (Box 607)
    - Bicentennial Commission (Box 607)
    - Business (Box 607)
    - Conferences, Miscellaneous (Box 608)
    - Congressional Clearinghouse on Women's Rights (Box 608)
    - Conventions on Political Rights of Women, U.N. and Inter-American (Box 608)
    - Credit: (Box 609)
      - Correspondence (Box 609)
      - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda, Statements and Releases (Box 609)
      - General (Box 609)
      - Federal Reserve Board (Box 609)
      - Hearings and Testimony (Box 610)
      - Legislation:
        - 92nd Congress and n.d. (Box 610)
        - 93rd Congress (Box 610)
        - 94th Congress (Box 610)
      - Reports (Box 611)
      - Printed (Box 611)
      - Divorce (Box 611)
      - Economic Statistics (Box 611)
      - Education: (Box 612)
        - Correspondence, Notes and Memoranda (Box 612)
        - General (Box 612)
        - Association of American Colleges Project (Box 612)
        - Legislation (Box 612)
        - Reports (Box 612)
        - Vocational Education (Box 612)
        - Printed (Box 612)
        - Title IX: (Box 613)
        - Correspondence (Box 613)
        - Abzug--Statements, Notes and Memoranda (Box 613)
        - General (Box 613)
        - Association of American Colleges (Box 613)
        - Health, Education and Welfare, U.S. Dept. of-Memos and Publications (Box 613)
        - Hearings and Testimony (Box 614)
        - Legislation (Box 614)
        - Printed (Box 614)
    - Equal Rights Amendment:
      - Correspondence (Box 614)
      - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and statements (Box 615)
      - General (Box 615)
      - Hearings and Testimony (Box 615)
      - Legislation (Box 615)
      - New York State (Box 615)
      - Ratification (Box 615)
      - Printed (Box 616)
    - Federal Agencies, Programs and Contracts:
      - Correspondence, notes, memoranda and statements (Box 616)
      - General (Box 616)
      - Action (Barber Case) (Box 616)
      - Legislation (Box 616)
      - Printed (Box 616)
    - Foundations (Box 616)
    - Friedan, Betty (Box 616)
    - Health: (Box 617)
      - General (Box 617)
      - Diethylstilbestrol (DES) (Box 617)
      - Planned Parenthood--Family Planning/Population Reporter; Washington Reporter (Box 617)
    - Homemakers (Box 617)
    - Insurance--Health, Disability, Workers' Compensation, and General (Box 617)
    - Insurance, Unemployment (Box 618)
    - International Women's Almanac (Box 618)
    - International Women's Year (IWY):
      - Correspondence (Box 618)
      - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and statements (Box 618)
      - General (Box 618)
    - I.W.Y.: (Box 619)
      - Bulletin (Box 619)
      - Conference, Mexico City:
        - Abzug--Notes, Memos, statements, and Activities (Box 619)
        - General (Box 619)
        - Agenda Items 1-10 (Box 619)
        - Agenda Item 11--World Plan of Action (Box 619)
        - Meetings and Schedules (Box 620)
        - Messages and Opening Statements (Box 620)
        - Reports (Box 620)
        - United Nations Documents (Box 620)
        - United States Delegation (Box 620)
        - U.S.I.S. News Summaries (Box 620)
      - Conferences, National:
        - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda, Statements and Releases (Box 620)
        - General (Box 620)
      - Legislation: (Box 621)
        - Correspondence and "Dear Colleague" letters (Box 621)
        - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda an Statements General (Box 621)
        - Hearings and Testimony (Box 621)
        - Organizational Support (Box 621)
        - Printed (Box 621)
      - Conferences, National: (Box 622)
        - Opposition (Box 622)
        - Personnel (Box 622)
      - Congressional Symposium (Box 622)
      - Homemakers (Box 622)
      - Lawsuit (Box 622)
      - Legislation and Appropriations (Box 622)
      - Lobbying Regulations (Box 622)
      - National Commission:
        - Correspondence (Box 622)
        - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and statements (Box 622)
        - General (Box 623)
        - Committees:
          - General (1 volume, 1 Folder) (Box 623)
          - Arts and Humanities (Box 624)
          - Coordinating (Box 624)
          - Government Organization Structure (Box 624)
          - Correspondence (Box 624)
          - Abzug--Notes, Memos, Statements (Box 624)
          - General (Box 624)
          - Legislation, Proposed (Box 624)
          - Recommendations (Box 624)
          - Special Problems of Women (Box 625)
          - Women in Power (Box 625)
        - Finances (Box 625)
        - Meetings, Agendas and Minutes (Box 625)
        - Office of Public Information (Box 625)
        - Press Releases, White House (Box 625)
        - Recommendations (Box 625)
        - Printed; Photograph (Box 625)
      - Reports, Miscellaneous (Box 626)
      - State, U. S. Department of (Box 626)
      - United Nations--miscellaneous (Box 626)
      - U.S. Center for International Women' s Year (Box 626)
      - International Women's Network (Box 626)
      - Printed (Box 626)
    - Jewish Women (Box 627)
    - Kennedy, Jane (Box 627)
    - Labor and Employment:
      - Correspondence, Notes and Statements (Box 627)
      - General (Box 627)
      - American Telephone and Telegraph Company (Box 627)
      - Apprenticeships (Box 627)
      - Federally Employed Women (FEW) (Box 627)
      - Flight Attendants (Box 628)
      - Hearings and Testimony (Box 628)
      - House Beauty Shop (Box 628)
      - Labor, U.S. Department of--Publications (Box 628)
      - Legislation (Box 628)
      - Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs (Box 628)
      - Pensions (Box 628)
      - Statistics (Box 628)
      - Unions (Box 628)
      - Womanpower (Box 628)
      - Printed (Box 628)
    - Lawsuits (Box 629)
    - Legislation:
      - 92nd; 93rd; 94th Congresses (Box 629)
      - Maternity:
        - Correspondence and notes (Box 629)
        - General (Box 629)
        - Employment and Benefits (Box 629)
        - Legislation (Box 630)
        - Printed (Box 630)
    - Media (Box 630)
    - Military (Box 630)
    - Names and Prefixes:
      - Correspondence (Box 630)
      - General (Box 630)
      - Legislation (Box 631)
      - Passports (Box 631)
      - Printed (Box 631)
    - New York City and State (Box 631)
    - Organizations:
      - General (Box 631)
      - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 631)
      - Federally Employed Women (FEW) (Box 631)
      - National Council of Women (Box 631)
      - National Organization for Women (NOW) (Box 632)
      - National Women's Education Fund (Box 632)
      - U. S. National Women's Agenda (Box 632)
      - Women Strike for Peace (Box 632)
      - Women's Action Alliance (Box 632)
      - Women's Equity Action League (WEAL) (Box 632)
      - Women's Lobby, Inc. (Box 632)
      - Working Women United (Box 632)
    - Paul, Alice (Box 632)
    - Policewomen:
      - Correspondence (Box 632)
      - Abzug--Notes and Memoranda (Box 632)
      - General (Box 633)
      - Lawsuits--Acha vs. Beame (Box 633)
      - Lawsuits--Acha vs. Beame; others (Box 633)
      - Legislation (Box 633)
      - Reports (Box 634)
      - Printed (Box 634)
    - Politics:
      - General (Box 634)
      - Democratic Party (Box 634)
      - National Women's Political Caucus (Box 634)
    - Prisons (Box 635)
    - Prostitution (Box 635)
    - Rankin, Jeanette (Box 635)
    - Rape:
      - Correspondence (Box 635)
      - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and Statements (Box 635)
      - General (Box 635)
      - Law and Legislation (Box 635)
      - Reports and Pamphlets (Box 635)
      - Printed (Box 636)
    - Raymond, Jill (Box 636)
    - Reports (Box 636)
    - Resource and Reading Lists and Rosters (Box 636)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission and Stock Exchange (Box 636)
    - Silkwood, Karen (Box 636)
    - Social Security: (Box 637)
      - Correspondence (SEE ALSO: SOCIAL SECURITY--Women) (Box 637)
      - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda and Statements (Box 637)
      - General (Box 637)
      - Disability (Box 637)
      - Hearings and Testimony (Box 637)
      - Homemakers:
        - Correspondence (Box 637)
        - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda, Statements and Releases (Box 637)
        - General (Box 637)
    - Social Security--Homemakers--legislation (Box 638)
    - Supreme Court:
      - General (Box 638)
      - Stevens, John P.--nomination (Box 638)
    - Women's Equality Day:
      - Correspondence (Box 638)
      - Abzug--Notes, Memoranda, Statements and Releases (Box 638)
      - General (Box 638)
    - Printed: (Box 638)
    - Women Today (Box 638)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 638)
  - Subseries V.55: Youth
    - Correspondence (Box 639)
    - General (Box 639)
    - Boy Scouts (Box 639)
    - Girl Scouts (Box 639)
    - Legislation (Box 639)
    - National Youth Caucus (Box 639)
    - New Future Foundation (Box 640)
    - New York City:
      - General (Box 640)
      - Chinese Youth Council (Box 640)
      - Gangs (Box 640)
      - Little League Baseball, Inwood (Box 640)
      - Youth Services Agency (Box 640)
    - White House Conference on Youth (Box 640)
    - "Youth in the Arts" Project (Maya Warwick) (Box 640)
    - Printed (Box 640)
- Series VI: Legislative Files
  - Subseries VI.1: Legislative Floor Files
    Legislative Floor Files. Chronological files of material relating to legislation considered on the House floor. Included are correspondence, drafts of amendments, statements and testimony, memoranda, Whip advisories, floor calendars, printed versions of legislation, and related material. In some cases, partial contents notes are included on the Folders as they were on the original Folders, to indicate some of the important issues dealt with in a particular week; these are in no way indications of the complete contents. The files are arranged by week through 1974 and thereafter by date.
    - 1 March 1971 HR 4690 Public Debt Increase (Box 641)
    - 8 March 1971 HR 4246 Wage & Price; HR 5432 Interest Equality (Box 641)
    - 15 March 1971 Supersonic transport (Box 641)
    - 22 March 1971 18 year old vote; Vietnam Special Order; House restaurant (Box 641)
    - 29 March 1971 Draft (Box 641)
    - 5 April 1971 Education; Feed grain (no vote) (Box 641)
    - 19 April 1971 HR 5376 Public Works acceleration (Box 641)
    - 26 April 1971 (Box 641)
    - 3 May 1971 (Box 641)
    - 10 May 1971 (Box 641)
    - 17 May 1971 (Box 642)
    - 24 May 1971 Reorganization of Vista (Box 642)
    - 1 June 1971 Legislative authorizations; NASA;: Emergency employment (Box 642)
    - 7 June 1971 Wagner/O' Day; Sugar Act (Box 642)
    - 17 June 1971 (Box 642)
    - 21 June 1971 (Box 642)
    - 28 June 1971 Space shuttle: Mansfield (draft (Box 643)
    - 5 July 1971 Resolution of Inquiry II (Box 643)
    - 12 July 1971 CBS contempt Cannikin (Box 643)
    - 19 July 1971 (Box 643)
    - 26 July 1971, (2 Folders) (Box 644)
    - 2 August 1971 Foreign aid; Selective Service Conference Report (Box 644)
    - 6 September 1971 Marine Sanctuaries (Box 644)
    - 13 September 1971 Detention camps; E.E.O.C. (Box 644)
    - 20 September 1971 (Box 645)
    - 27 September 1971 v O.E.C. Resolution of Inquiry--Vietnam Elections (Box 645)
    - 4 October 1971 N.E.P.; E.R.A. (Box 645)
    - 11 October 1971 E.R.A.; Consumer protection (Box 645)
    - 18 October 1971 School lunch: Alaska natives; Mansfield II (Box 645)
    - 26 October 1971 Military construction appropriations; Higher education (Box 645)
    - 1 November 1971 Higher education (Box 645)
    - 8 November 1971 Prayer: Pesticides (Box 646)
    - 15 November 1971 (Box 646)
    - 29 November 1971 Election spending; D.C. appropriations: Sale of ships (Box 646)
    - 6 December 1971 O.E.O./Child care (Conference Report); Foreign Assistance Appropriations; Phase II (Box 646)
    - 13 December 1971 Economic Stability Conference Report (Rent Amendment): Defense Appropriations Conference Report (Box 646)
    - 18 January 1972 (Box 647)
    - 24 January 1972 Foreign Aid Authorization Conference Report (Box 647)
    - 31 January 1972 (Box 647)
    - 7 February 1972 Debt Limit: Dock Strike (Box 647)
    - 14 February 1972 O.E.O. (Box 647)
    - 21 February 1972 (Box 647)
    - 28 February 1972 H.I.S.C. Funds (Box 647)
    - 6 March 1972 (Box 648)
    - 13 March 1972 (Box 648)
    - 20 March 1972 (Box 648)
    - 27 March 1972 Water pollution (empty Folder) (Box 648)
    - 10 Apri11972 (Box 648)
    - 17 April 1972 (Box 648)
    - 24 April 1972 (Box 648)
    - 1 May 1972 (Box 648)
    - 8 May 1972 (Box 648)
    - 8 May 1972 Minimum Wage (HR 7130) (Box 648)
    - 15 May 1972 (Box 649)
    - 22 May 1972 (Box 649)
    - 30 May 1972 (Box 649)
    - 5 June 1972 A.E.C.: Higher education (Box 649)
    - 12 June 1972 (Box 649)
    - 19 June 1972 Revenue sharing (Box 649)
    - 26 June 1972 (Box 649)
    - 17 July 1972 (Box 650)
    - 24 July 1972 (Box 650)
    - 31 July 1972 (Box 650)
    - 7 August 1972 (Box 650)
    - 7 August 1972 Foreign aid (Box 650)
    - 14 August 1972 (Box 650)
    - 14 August 1972 Busing (Box 650)
    - 5 September 1972 (Box 651)
    - 11 September 1972 (Box 651)
    - 11 September 1972 Defense appropriations, FY 1973 (Box 651)
    - 18 September 1972 Labor/H..E.\v. appropriations; Consumer safety: Foreign aid appropriations (Box 651)
    - 25 September 1972 Gateway (Box 651)
    - 2 October 1972 (Box 651)
    - 9 October 1972 Debt ceiling; Supplemental appropriations (Box 652)
    - 16 October 1972 HR 1 Conference Report (Box 652)
    - 5 February 1973 (Box 652)
    - 19 February 1973 (Box 652)
    - 26 February 1973 (Box 652)
    - 5 March 1973 (Box 652)
    - 12 March 1973 E.D.A.; Older Americans (Box 653)
    - 19 March 1973 (Box 653)
    - 26 March 1973 (Box 653)
    - 2 April1973 (Box 653)
    - 9 April1973 Franking (Box 653)
    - 16 April 1973 Economic stability; Highways (Box 653)
    - 30 Apri11973 (Box 653)
    - 7 May 1973 Supplemental appropriations; Cambodia (Box 653)
    - 15 May 1973 (Box 654)
    - 21 May 1973 NASA authorization (shuttle) (Box 654)
    - 28 May 1973 (Box 654)
    - 4 June 1973 (Box 654)
    - 4 June 1973 Minimum wage (Box 654)
    - 11 June 1973 (Box 654)
    - 18 June 1973 Department of Transportation appropriations: L.E.A.A.; H.U.D.; Space appropriations (Box 655)
    - 18 June 1973 Legal Services (21 June 1973) (Box 655)
    - 18 June 1973 Columbia reactor (Box 655)
    - 25 June 1973 Labor/H.E W. appropriations; War Powers; A. E. C. .Authorization appropriations State, Justice and Commerce Department appropriations (Box 655)
    - 9 July 1973 (Box 656)
    - 16 July 1973 (Box 656)
    - 16 July 1973 Agriculture--Food stamps (Box 656)
    - 16 July 1973 Agricultural Extension Act (Box 656)
    - 16 July 1973 Impoundment (Box 656)
    - 23 July 1973 (Box 656)
    - 30 July 1973 (Box 656)
    - 5 September 1973 (Box 657)
    - 10 September 1973 (Box 657)
    - 17 September 1973 (Box 657)
    - 24 September 1973 (Box 657)
    - 1 October 1973 (Box 658)
    - 8 October 1973 (Box 658)
    - 8 October 1973 D.C. Home Rule (Box 658)
    - 15 October 1973 (Box 658)
    - 22 October 1973 (Box 658)
    - 29 October 1973 HR 9286--Military Procurement Conference (Box 658)
    - Report; HR 9456--Drug Abuse Education (Box 658)
    - 5 November 1973 (Box 659)
    - 12 November 1973 Alaska Pipeline Conference Report (Box 659)
    - 26 November 1973 (Box 659)
    - 3 December 1973 Saxbe emoluments; Labor/H.E.W. Conference Report; Ford Nomination (Box 659)
    - 3 December 1973 Budget and Impoundment Control Act (Box 659)
    - 3 December 1973 Foreign Aid Authorization (Box 659)
    - 3 December 1973 Military Construction Appropriations (Box 659)
    - 10 December 1973 Emergency Energy Act (Box 660)
    - 10 December 1973 Trade Reform Act (10710); Foreign Aid Appropriations (Box 660)
    - 10 December 1973 Trade Reform Act (10710) (Box 660)
    - 17 December 1973, (2 Folders) (Box 660)
    - January-.June1974 NOT RECEIVED; See Also Box TT (Box 660)
    - 19 .July 1974 Cattle loans (Box 661)
    - 22 .July 1974 Defense Production Act (13044) (Box 661)
    - 22 .July 1974 Interior Appropriations FY 1975 (Box 661)
    - 22 .July 1974 Small Business Administration (15578) (Box 661)
    - 22 .July 1974 Strip Mining (11500) (Box 661)
    - 29 .July 1974 (Box 661)
    - 29 .July 1974 Agriculture/Environment/Consumer (HR 15472) (Box 661)
    - 29 .July 1974 A.S.C. Omnibus (Box 661)
    - 29 .Ju1y 1974 District Day Bills (Box 661)
    - 29 July 1974 Legislative Branch Appropriations Conference Report (Box 661)
    - 29 .July 1974 Treasury/Posta1 Service (HR 15544) Conference Report (Box 661)
    - 5 August 1974 (Box 662)
    - 5 August 1974 Defense Appropriations (HR 16243) Report (Box 662)
    - 5 August 1974 Election Campaign Reform (Box 662)
    - 5 August 1974 Military Construction (Box 662)
    - 5 August 1974 Real Estate Settlement (Box 662)
    - 12 August 1974 (Box 663)
    - 12 August 1974 D. C. Medical (Box 663)
    - 12 August 1974 Export Administration Act (HR 15264) (Box 663)
    - 12 August 1974 Export-Import Bank (HR 15977) (Box 663)
    - 12 .August 1974 Health Revenue Sharing (HR 14214) (Box 663)
    - 12 August 1974 Public Works Conference Report (Box 663)
    - 12 August 1974 Real Estate Settlement (HR 9989) (Box 663)
    - 12 August 1974 Transportation Department (HR 15404) Conference Report (Box 663)
    - 12 August 1974 Treasury/Post Office Conference Report (Box 663)
    - 19 August 1974 (Box 663)
    - 19 August 1974 Conference Reports (Box 663)
    - 19 August 1974 Consents (Box 663)
    - 19 August 1974 D.C. Appropriations Conference Report (HR 15581) (Box 663)
    - 19 August 1974 Foreign Investment Study Act (HR 15487) (Box 663)
    - 19 August 1974 Interior Appropriations Conference Report, FY 1975 (Box 663)
    - 19 August 1974 Pensions (Box 663)
    - 19 August 1974 State Department Authorizations (Box 663)
    - 19 August 1974 Suspensions (Box 663)
    - 3 September 1974 (Box 664)
    - 9 September 1974 (Box 664)
    - 9 September 1974 Railroad Retirement Act (HR 15301) (Box 664)
    - 16 September 1974 (Box 664)
    - 16 September 1974 Consumer warranties (7917) (Box 664)
    - 16 September 1974 Solar Energy Research and Development (Box 664)
    - 16 September 1974 Suspensions (Box 664)
    - 23 September 1974 (Box 664)
    - 23 September 1974 Copper penny/Eisenhower College (HR 16032) (Box 664)
    - 23 September 1974 Defense Department Appropriations Conference Report (Box 664)
    - 23 September 1974 Supplemental Appropriations--Nixon transition/ Holt amendment (Box 664)
    - 30 September 1974 (Box 664)
    - 30 September 1974 Committee Reform (Box 664)
    - 30 September 1974 Supplemental Appropriations--Agriculture Environment (Box 664)
    - 7 October 1974 (Box 665)
    - 7 October 1974 Privacy (Box 665)
    - 14 October 1974 (Box 665)
    - 11 November 1974 (Box 665)
    - 18 November 1974 (Box 666)
    - 18 November 1974 A.E.C. Reports to Congress (HR 16074) (Box 666)
    - 18 November 1974 Conference Report (Box 666)
    - 18 November 1974 Freedom of Information Veto Override (Box 666)
    - 18 November 1974 Safe Drinking Water (HR 13002) (Box 666)
    - 18 November 1974 Suspension (Box 666)
    - 18 November 1974 Suspension (Box 666)
    - 25 November 1974 Veto Override (Box 666)
    - 2 December 1974 Asian Development Bank (Box 667)
    - 2 December 1974 Budget Recession (HR 17505) (Box 667)
    - 2 December 1974 Nurse Training, Health Manpower Acts (HR 17084/5) (Box 667)
    - 2 December 1974 Strip Mining (Box 667)
    - 2 December 1974 Suspensions (Box 667)
    - 2 Dec 1974 Suspensions and White House Library (Box 667)
    - 9 December 1974 HR 17597 (Box 667)
    - 9 December 1974 American Film Institute (Box 667)
    - 9 December 1974 Surface Transportation (Box 667)
    - 9 December 1974 Suspensions (Box 667)
    - 16 December 1974 (Box 667)
    - 16 December 1974 Rice Act (Box 667)
    - 16 December 1974 Suspensions (Box 667)
    - 4 February 1975 Food Stamps (Box 668)
    - 5 February 1975 Oil Imports/Public Debt (Box 668)
    - 19 February 1975 (Box 668)
    - 25 February 1975 (Box 668)
    - 27 February 1975 (Box 668)
    - 4 March 1975 (Box 668)
    - 10 March 1975 (Box 668)
    - 11 March 1975 Israeli Reactor Research (Box 668)
    - 12 March 1975 (Box 668)
    - 17 March 1975 Suspension Calendar (Box 668)
    - 18 March 1975 Strip Mining Amendments (Box 668)
    - 19 March 1975 Agriculture Bill (Box 668)
    - 21 March 1975 Emergency Middle Income Housing (HR 4485) (Box 668)
    - 24 March 1975 Nutrition Act Amendment (Box 668)
    - 25 March 1975 (Box 668)
    - 8 April1975 (Box 669)
    - 9 Apri1 1975 National Science Foundation (Box 669)
    - 9 April 1975 NASA Authorizations; Standard Reference Data (Box 669)
    - 10 April1975 (Box 669)
    - 14 April 1975 Emergency Homeowners Relief Act (HR 5398) (Box 669)
    - 15 April 1975 Second Supplemental (Box 669)
    - 16 April 1975 (Box 669)
    - 17 April 1975 (Box 669)
    - 21 April 1975 Highways: Per Diem (Box 669)
    - 22 April 1975 Small Business; Agriculture (Box 669)
    - 24 April 1975 Amtrack: S.E.C. (Box 669)
    - 30 Apri1 1975 Budget (Box 669)
    - 5 May 1975 (Box 669)
    - 6 May 1975 (Box 669)
    - 7 May 1975 Nurse Training Act (HR 4115); Health Service Corps (HR 4114) (Box 669)
    - 8 May 1975 Variable interest rate mortgages (Box 670)
    - 12 May 1975 Budget recession; Maritime authorizations (Box 670)
    - 13 May 1975 Agriculture veto override (Box 670)
    - 14 May 1975 Vietnam; Budget: Emergency employment (Box 670)
    - 19 May 1975 $2 million O.E.O. authorization (HR 6054) (Box 670)
    - 19 May 1975 Appalachian Regional Development Act (Box 670)
    - 19 May 1975 Coast Guard appropriations (HR 5217) (Box 670)
    - 19 May 1975 Marine Protection and Sanctuaries Act (HR 5710 (Box 670)
    - 19 May 1975 Extend Offshore Shrimp Fisheries Act of 1973 (HR 5709) (Box 670)
    - 20 May 1975 I.W.Y.: Public Works Bill (Box 670)
    - 21 May 1975 Vietnam Aid Conference Report; Parole: Unemployment benefits (Box 670)
    - 22 May 1975 Securities Acts Amendments Conference Report (Box 670)
    - 3 .June 1975 Equal Credit Opportunity; Forest Pest Control; Postal reorganization: Emergency Livestock Credit Acts (Box 670)
    - 4 .June 1975 Voting Rights (Box 670)
    - 4 June 1975 Emergency Employment Veto Override (Box 670)
    - 5 June 1915 Health Revenue Sharing (Box 670)
    - 5 June 1975 Emergency Housing Act: Review of Decontrol of .Petroleum Prices (Box 670)
    - 11 June 1975 Strip Mining Bill (HR 25): Urgent Supplemental Appropriations (HJRes 492) (Box 671)
    - 16 June 1975 Higher Education Act amendment; Public Debt Limitation; Suspension Calendar (12 bills) (Box 671)
    - 17 June 1975 Suspension; Appropriations FY 1976 Continuing Appropriations (Box 671)
    - 19 June 1975 Energy Bill (Box 671)
    - 19 June 1975 Debt Limitation (Box 671)
    - 20 June 1975 Duty & Tariff (Box 671)
    - 23 June 1975 State Department Authorization Act, FYs 1976, 1977 (HR 7500): Plutonium transport restrictions; Appropriations committee (Box 671)
    - 23 June 1975 Peace Corps (HR 6334) (Box 671)
    - 23 June 1975 Railroad Safety (Box 671)
    - 23 June 1975 Credit Uses (Box 671)
    - 23 June 1975 Criminal Procedure Act Amendments (Box 671)
    - 24 June 1975 Debt Limitation (Box 671)
    - 24 June 1915 H.U.D.; Space shuttle; National Science Foundation (Box 671)